(抱歉 车很脏)
滚开
Go away!
(惠伦有限责任合伙律所)
(搭车者可能为逃犯)
《行尸走肉》
然后就是你和贝丝两个人了吗？
It was just you and Beth after?
- 是啊 - 你救了她吗？
- Yeah. - You save her?
她很坚强 她救了自己
She's tough. She saved herself.
我们一起流浪了一段时间
We were out there for a while.
我们被困住了 她先闯出去了 然后…
We got cornered, she got out in front of me and...
我不知道 她不见了
I don't know, she was gone.
我出来时 一辆车开走了
I came out and a car's pulling out
车窗上有白十字
with a white cross on the window.
- 就像那辆车吗？- 是的
- Just like that one? - Yep.
瑞克会想知道我们去了哪里
Rick's gonna wonder where we went.
油箱里快没油了
Tank's running low.
我们能很快结束这一切 把他撞下公路就行
We can end this quick. Just run him off the road.
不 远远跟着就行了
Nah, we're good for a bit.
如果他们把她关在了某个地方
If they're holding her somewhere,
我们可以逼问司机
we can get it out of the driver.
是啊 但如果他不肯开口 我们又回到起点了
Yeah, but if he don't talk, we're back to square one.
现在我们有优势
Right now we got the advantage.
我们会搞清他们的身份
We'll see who they are.
如果他们是一伙人 看看他们的实力
If they're a group, see what they can do.
然后我们就去尽力救她回来
And then we'll do what we gotta do to get her back.
他们在往北边走 I-85公路
They're heading north, I-85.
他在等什么呢？
What the hell's he waiting for?
有两个人
There's two of them.
那是警察吗？
Is that a cop?
他们可能看见我们了
They might've seen us.
该死 油箱没油了
Aw, shit! Tank's tapped.
他们本可以走支路的 但他们没有
They'd have taken the bypass and they didn't.
他们肯定藏身在城市的某个地方
They must be holed up in the city somewhere.
我们得走了 找个地方藏起来 等到天亮
We gotta move, find someplace to hole up till sunlight.
我知道一个地方 离这里就几个街区
I know a place just a couple of blocks from here.
我们能过去
We can make it.
- 又来了两只 - 就快打开了
- Two more. - I almost got it.
快点
Come on.
你以前在这工作过吗？
You used to work here or something?
差不多吧
Something.
- 这是哪？- 临时住所
- What's this place? - It's temporary housing.
(治疗童年受虐者)
你来过？
You came here?
没留多久
We didn't stay.
我睡上铺
I'll take the top bunk.
下铺更适合你
I think that one's more your style.
你睡吧 我先守夜
You should sleep. I'll take first watch.
- 这里封锁得很严 - 我知道
- This is locked up pretty tight. - I know.
那就很安全啊
Then we're good, then.
我想守夜 我不介意
I'll keep first watch. I don't mind.
随你
Suit yourself.
你说我们可以重新开始
You said we get to start over.
是
Yeah.
你这样做了吗？
Did you?
我在努力
I'm trying.
你想说什么就说吧？
Why don't you say what's really on your mind?
我觉得我们不会再继续救人了
I don't think we get to save people anymore.
那你为什么来这里？
Then why are you here?
我在努力
I'm trying.
我们在车旁边的时候…
When we were out by the car...
要是我没有出现呢
what if I didn't show up?
我还是不知道
I still don't know.
你不必这样做
You don't have to.
不必
You don't.
谢谢
Thank you.
车是往市中心去的
That car was headed downtown.
我们找一栋高楼
I say we get up in one of the tall ones,
登高望远 看看情况
get ourselves a view, see what we see.
我们可以沿着建筑物潜行
We can stay close to the buildings and keep quiet,
但迟早还是会引到行尸
but sooner or later, we're gonna be drawing them.
好 可以从那儿上去 有座桥
All right, we can get up there. There's a bridge.
有时候 我真是已经麻木无语了
Some days, I don't know what the hell to think.
幸好我们没吃早饭
Good thing we skipped breakfast.
我们怎么到这来了？
How did we get here?
就这么来了
We just did.
你还没问"发生了什么事"
You still haven't asked me what happened.
我遇到泰尔西和姑娘们之后
After I met up with Tyreese, the girls.
我知道发生了什么
Yeah, I know what happened.
她们没来
They ain't here.
比这还糟
It was worse than that.
我之所以说我们要重新开始…
The reason I said we get to start over...
是因为我们必须这么做
is because we gotta.
像从前一样…
The way it was...
是的
Yeah.
你看到什么了？
You see something?
我也不知道 把枪给我
I don't know. Hand me that rifle.
就在那
Right there.
已经在那停了一段时间了
It's been there a while.
肯定是那些人的车
Definitely one of them.
肯定是个线索
It's definitely some kind of lead.
我们赶紧补给吧
We should fill up.
好吧
All right.
怎么了？
What?
我猜这肯定花了某个阔佬一大笔钱
I bet this cost some rich prick a lot of money.
就像一只狗坐在了油墨上
Looks like a dog sat in paint,
在整张画里蹭屁股
wiped its ass all over the place.
真的吗？我还挺喜欢的
Really? I kinda like it.
得了吧
Stop.
我是认真的
I'm serious.
你又不了解我
You don't know me.
是啊 继续骗自己吧
Yep, you keep telling yourself that.
- 别出来 达里尔 - 站起来
- Daryl, don't. - Get up.
举起手来 你们俩
Hands up, both of you.
放下弩
Lay down your crossbow.
你真是有种
You got some sack on you.
听着 我不想伤害任何人
Look, nobody has to get hurt.
我只是需要武器 就这样
I just need weapons, that's it.
所以请放下弩
So, please, lay down your crossbow.
后退
Back up.
抱歉了
Sorry about this.
你们看上去挺强的
You look tough.
你们会没事的
You'll be all right.
还剩三发子弹
Three bullets.
我们困在市中心 他抢了我们的武器
We're in the middle of a city. He was stealing our weapons.
你觉得我刚才是要杀他吗？
Did you think I was gonna kill him?
我瞄的是他的腿
I was aiming for his leg.
有可能会杀了他吗？可能吧 说不准
Could that have killed him? Maybe, I don't know.
但是他抢了我们的武器
But he was stealing our weapons.
他只是个孩子
He's a damn kid.
没有武器我们会死
Without weapons we could die.
贝丝会死
Beth could die.
我们会找到更多武器的
We'll find more weapons.
我不想让你死
I don't want you to die.
我不想让贝丝死
I don't want Beth to die.
我不想让教堂里的任何人死
I don't want anybody at the church to die,
但我也不能眼睁睁地看着他们死
but I can't stand around and watch it happen either.
我不能 所以我走了
I can't. That's why I left.
我只是必须去别的地方
I just had to be somewhere else.
你不在别的地方 你就在这里
Well, you ain't somewhere else; you're right here.
在努力着
Trying.
你不再是以前的你了 我也不是了
Look, you're not who you were and neither am I.
我不知道我还相不相信上帝和天堂
I don't know if I believe in God anymore or heaven,
但是如果我以后会下地狱 我要尽可能
but if I'm going to hell, I'm making damn sure
拖得久一点
I'm holding it off as long as I can.
(治疗童年受虐者)
好了 我们开始吧
All right, let's get this done.
车不稳 我体重轻点
It's not stable. I'm lighter.
越来越多了
There's more coming.
我们得杀出去
We're gonna have to fight through.
是啊 我看见它们了
Yeah, I see them.
我们得走了
We have to go.
GMH 那是什么？医院吗？
GMH, what's that? A hospital?
不知道 可能是格拉迪纪念医院吧？
I don't know. Grady Memorial, maybe?
格拉迪 白十字 可能他们就藏在那里
Grady, the white crosses... it might be where they're holing up.
达里尔
Daryl!
快走 快走
Go, go, go, go!
有没有能利用的东西？
Anything we can use?
除了我们自己带的 再无其他
Nothin' but what we got.
好吧
All right,
系好安全带
buckle up.
你抓牢
You hold on.
我们没事
We're okay.
- 我们还活着 - 上帝
- We're okay. - God.
给
Here.
我没事
I'm fine.
证明给我看
Prove it.
你伤得重吗？
How bad is it?
我经历过更糟的
I've had worse.
该死 那样真愚蠢
Damn, that was stupid.
那样下来更快
We made good time down.
我们和格拉迪医院之间只隔着三个街区了
There's only three blocks between us and Grady.
我们得在附近找个地方
We need to find a place nearby,
观察一下那里 看看能发现什么
scope it out, see what we can see.
你认为只用看 我们就能搞清楚
You really think we're gonna find out what we need to know
我们需要了解的事吗？
just by watching?
我们从观察入手
It's where we start.
走吧
Come on.
是他们
It's them.
很好
All right.
我们开始观察吧
Let's see what we see.
你说我现在跟以前不一样了吗？
You said I ain't like how I was before?
是的
Yeah.
那我以前什么样？
How was I?
你以前像个孩子
It's like you were a kid.
现在长大成人了
Now you're a man.
那你呢？
What about you?
我和索菲亚在那个庇护所待了一天半
Me and Sophia stayed at that shelter for a day and a half
然后回到爱德那里
before I went running back to Ed.
我回到家 被暴打一顿
I went home, I got beat up,
生活继续 然后…
life went on, and ...
我只是不停地祈祷可以发生一些事情
I just kept praying for something to happen.
但我什么也没做
But I didn't do anything.
他妈什么都没做
Not a damn thing.
跟他在一起的那个我…
When I was with him...
她已经死掉了
she got burned away.
这让我感到开心 也不是开心 但就是…
And I was happy about that. I mean, not happy, but...
在监狱的时候
and at the prison
我成为了我一直认为自己应该成为的人
I got to be who I always thought I should be,
我早该成为的人
thought I should've been.
但是她也死掉了
And then she got burned away.
现在的一切都只是…
Everything now just...
在燃烧消耗你
consumes you.
我们又不是灰烬
We ain't ashes.
是你的箭吗？
Is that yours?
是啊
Yeah.
天呐
Oh, God.
我没事
I'm good.
我没事 你快走
I'm good. You go.
天呐
God.
求你了 我总得保护自己啊
Plea... please. I had to protect myself.
- 你为什么跟着我们？- 我没有
- Why you following us? - I-I didn't,
我发誓 我以为你们在跟踪我
I swear! I thought you followed me.
扯蛋
Bullshit.
拜托 兄弟 求你了
Come on, man. Plea... please!
- 求你了 - 不行 我已经救过你一次了
- Please, please. - Nah, I already helped you once.
不可能再救你了
It ain't happening again.
跟那个行尸好好玩吧
Have fun with Hoss over there.
不不不
No. No, no, no.
不不不 求你了 求你了
No. No, no, no! Please! Please!
求你了 对不起 求你了
Please! I'm sorry, please!
- 求你了 求你了 - 达里尔 停下
- Please! Please, please! - Daryl. Daryl. Stop.
- 你差点因为他死掉 - 但我没死
- You almost died because of him! - But I didn't.
不行 随他去吧
Nah, let him be.
- 对不起 求你了 对不起 - 达里尔
- I'm sorry. Please, I'm sorry! - Daryl!
加把劲 再出来点
Come on, just a little more.
谢谢 谢谢 谢谢
Thank you. Thank you. Thank you.
你没事吧？
You okay?
还活着呢
I'm still here.
我得走了 我得走了
I gotta go. I gotta go.
他们会来的 他们应该听到枪声了
They're gonna come. They probably heard the shot.
如果他们找到我…
If they find me...
- 谁？- 他们 医院的人
- Who? - Them, people at the hospital.
等等 告诉我们 那里有没有一个金发女孩？
Wait, wait, wait, just tell us... is there a blonde girl there?
- 你见过一个金发女孩吗？- 贝丝？
- You see a blonde girl? - Beth?
你认识她吗？
You know her?
她帮我逃了出来 但她还在里面
She helped me get out, but she's still there.
他们来了
They're coming.
我们得立刻走 我们得走了
We gotta go now. We gotta go. We gotta go.
隔壁的大楼有个地下室
The building next door has a basement.
那里没行尸 很安全
It's clear. We'll be safe.
快走 我扶他
Go, I got him.
快点 起来
Come on, get up.
- 起来 - 好的
- Get up. - Okay.
不 等等
No, no, no! Wait, wait, wait!
- 放开我 - 等等 他们能救她
- Let go of me! - Wait! They can help her.
只有他们能救她
They're the only ones who can.
他们有药 仪器 医生
They have medicine, machines, a doctor.
如果你出去 就必须杀了他们 好吗？
You go out there, you'll have to kill them, okay?
然后她就得不到救治了 你想这样吗？
And then she can't get their help. Is that what you want?
我们能救回她 我们能救回贝丝
We can get her back. We can get Beth back.
救她们要付出多大代价？
What's it gonna take?
很大
A lot.
他们有枪
They got guns,
有人
people.
我们也有
So do we.